{
    "subject": "Kenneth_Branagh",
    "predicate": "created",
    "object": "Love's_Labour's_Lost__2000_film_",
    "human_readable": "Kenneth Branagh created the film Love's Labour's Lost (2000).",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8535081744194031,
            "question": "What is the title of the film starring Kenneth Branagh released in 2000?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.842604398727417,
            "question": "What kind of work did Kenneth Branagh create in 2000?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8117826581001282,
            "question": "Which filmmaker created Love's Labour's Lost?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8083498477935791,
            "question": "What is the name of the film created by Kenneth Branagh?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7533003687858582,
            "question": "What year was the movie Love's Labour's Lost made?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7395504117012024,
            "question": "Who directed the film Love's Labour's Lost?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7048858404159546,
            "question": "What year was the film Love's Labour's Lost released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6076149940490723,
            "question": "Is Kenneth Branagh known for directing films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5827010273933411,
            "question": "Name a film directed by Kenneth Branagh."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5652462244033813,
            "question": "What is the genre of the film Love's Labour's Lost?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Kenneth Branagh created the film Love's Labour's Lost (2000).",
            "html": "yago_21974_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Name a film directed by Kenneth Branagh.",
            "html": "yago_21974_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Kenneth Branagh known for directing films?",
            "html": "yago_21974_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What year was the film Love's Labour's Lost released?",
            "html": "yago_21974_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21974_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21974_119.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21974_130.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21974_151.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21974_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21974_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21974_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21974_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21974_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21974_55.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports this triple. The files contain reviews and articles about the film adaptation of Shakespeare's \"Love's Labour's Lost\" by Kenneth Branagh, which was released in 2000. This indicates that he created the film in question."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents support that Kenneth Branagh directed and starred in the film adaptation of \"Love's Labour's Lost\" released in 2000. Therefore, the statement \"Kenneth Branagh created the film Love's Labour's Lost (2000)\" is correct according to the provided context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}